[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
[Disclaimer: This series is created solely for entertainment purposes.
All individuals, behaviors, places, and events depicted are entirely fictional,
with no intention to represent or reference any organizations, departments, occupations, or individuals]
But every time I dream,
it's always about her.
I used to be in here, didn't I?
But my feelings say otherwise.
I kissed you,
because I don't want to be just friends.
We still have hope.
What hope?
Chris...
will never love Nadear.
I'll help you out.
I want you to remember.
I'll make Chris
mine...
by any means necessary.
[Several days ago]
She's there.
I can't believe
that I'll get to see her again.
She seems to enjoy working out, huh?
If she isn't swimming,
she'll usually come to this park to run.
She really hasn't changed at all.
It's different, though.
She lost her memories.
What do you think?
Did she really forget about me?
She didn't keep her promise.
If she really has forgotten about me,
maybe I can finally let this go.
But I still want to make sure.
Carissa...
You really don't remember me?
♫The rain keeps splashing beneath our cover,♫
♫Once it was a special place for two lovers♫
♫There was never enough room for the third♫
♫Now, the rain soaks our hearts together♫
♫The question that's trapped in my heart♫
♫Maybe it's time for you to do your part♫
♫Choose the one your heart truly desires♫
♫Before the last raindrop falls, don't make me shed another tear♫
I knew what love was
when I first met you.
Her touch...
Her smell...
Chris.
I'll make things right
in three months.
Mm.
I'll wait for you no matter how long it takes.
Here.
Thanks.
Mm.
What will you do next?
It's just three months.
It's nothing compared to the four years I've waited.
You finally got her back, huh?
I already did it once.
Why can't I do it again?
If everything ends well, that's good.
But keep in mind
if Nadear asked her this,
it means
she's already planned what she will do next.
It's been four years,
and Chris still came back to me.
What can Nadear do?
Hold Chris back.
She managed to ask for three months.
Don't you think
that maybe she can keep asking for more time?
Actually...
Those three months
aren't just important to Nadear.
They're important to me too.
I don't know
if what we have between Chris and me
is really "love,"
or just an instinct.
A feeling of nostalgia.
So...
How are they different?
Because Chris lost her memories.
If our love
came from familiarity,
Chris might not choose me.
If over these three months,
our love blooms once more...
If it really is love,
I won't care about her past again.
Are you having a sleepover with your friends?
Mm.
That way, I'll get to leave my room.
Tell your friends that you want to spend some time with your girlfriend.
They'll think I'm avoiding them.
You worry about what your friends think,
but you don't worry if your girlfriend misses you?
Her hair smells faintly of shampoo.
Her hair is fine
and smooth.
She likes to tuck it behind her ears to keep it out of her face
when she bends down to kiss me on the bed.
Sun...
Sun.
Who is that?
How did you get in here?
I was worried you might have a nightmare,
so I came in to check on you as usual.
But what's happening between us isn't usual.
But we still have three months to get back to how it used to be.
And who is Sun?
A friend.
A friend who helped me come up with the flower dishes.
I think you're so stressed about the flower dishes
that you even dreamed about your friend.
I think you should rest.
Rest?
Your work.
Stop doing your work.
You've treated me like a sick person
for four whole years.
Hasn't that been more than enough?
- I'm just... - "Worried."
"Want what's best for me."
I've heard you say this hundreds of times now.
You want me to act normal,
but don't you realize our relationship was never normal to begin with?
I'm going to see my friend.
Here.
Thanks.
Everything is going smoothly.
It should open on schedule.
Well done.
So when are you opening?
Well, you said three more months.
I know.
I see you barely smiled today.
You seem stressed.
Is something bothering you?
It's about my dream.
Would you like to talk about it?
Not yet.
Alright,
as long as you're happy.
Okay.
[Verity Skin Clinic]
If I want to talk, I'll tell you.
Mm.
So it's really you, Sun.
[Third Person]
Sun, your junior.
How was she doing
after that accident four years ago?
Her brain injury
caused her to lose her memory temporarily.
Does this mean
she'll get better
soon, right?
Yes.
But...
We found that
Sun has a tumor near her brainstem.
When I first told you this,
you said you were Sun's friend, didn't you?
Yes,
we went to the same high school.
It's been four years.
Why did you come back
to ask me about this again?
Back then, you said Sun's father
took her overseas.
Yes,
she lost her memories,
so her father took the opportunity
to start her life anew over there.
I think Sun got her memories back.
If she's back...
If she got her memories back and came back,
why did no one know this?
You feel like...
you've known someone before?
If you like someone,
you can feel that way too.
It's like...
you've known each other for a long time.
You've heard of it before, yeah?
I think so too.
That means you like her.
I told you,
I'm trying to uphold
both my medical ethics
and my code as a friend.
I've felt that way ever since I first met her.
What made you curious about this?
I had a dream.
And I started dreaming more as we had more physical contact.
What are you curious about?
Well, if I used to know her...
What was our relationship like?
Would you like me to help?
I don't know...
It feels so familiar.
Familiar enough that I want to find the answer myself.
Why...
Why can't I find anything...?
What are you looking for?
Are you looking for someone named Sun?
Did you know
why I'm suspicious of you?
Because you dreamed,
but it wasn't the same.
Nadear...
Are you tired?
Not that much.
Thank you.
Let me massage you.
Yes,
back then, when I dreamed about our past,
I'd love Nadear even more.
I dreamed...
but it wasn't the same?
Can you make an effort
for these three months we still have?
My clinic is ready.
Would you like to come see it?
Why do you want to open a beauty clinic?
I thought you wanted to be a doctor and treat people.
Why do you think I like you?
It's because you're beautiful.
What?
You like me because of how I look?
Mm.
I want you to be my beautiful forever.
Then...can I be your only VIP customer forever?
Mm.
Forever.
I'm your first love, Chris.
What does that mean?
It's a way to bring you back to who you used to be.
I never liked it, though.
I don't like it either.
But it's for your own good.
You know
I'm willing to do anything for you.
What do you smell?
Roses...
And...
Where are you right now?
School...
What are you doing?
Copying my friend's homework.
So why did you smell roses?
Here.
Did you buy these to give to people?
No,
they're offerings for Buddha.
Then no thanks. I don't want to take one meant for Buddha.
This one isn't an offering.
I want to give it to you.
She gave it to me
before Buddhism class.
Hey, wait!
Chris!
Have you finished copying my homework?
Not yet. Are you going to turn it in now?
It's alright.
I'll wait until you're done.
Give me a sec.
Sun...
is my friend...?
What's wrong?
[Third Person]
Jeen.
Chris.
I think
Chris needs to rest.
Sun...
Sun.
Chris,
will you stop hurting yourself because of that woman?
Nadear, I'm at your front door.
We should talk.
Four years ago,
Chris's symptoms were very severe,
so you asked me
to help Chris live normally.
Yes,
you helped both Chris
and me.
Back then, Chris's brain
was like a clear, empty glass.
Whatever color we add,
that's what we'll see.
What are you implying?
Chris now has her own memories.
I'm not sure
her body can handle it
if we still keep this up.
All of Chris's memories
are too much
for the same clear glass to hold.
If remembering everything hurts her,
then I want her to remember that much.
I can't afford to lose her again.
Any updates on the flower dishes?
Chris is unwell. I'll tell you later.
Chris,
are you alright?
I'm in front of your house.
Can you come see me?
[Chris, are you alright?]
[I'm in front of your house. Can you come see me?]
This really looks like we're having an affair.
Why were you gone, then?
I couldn't contact you.
I'm sick.
You don't have a fever, though.
I'm a bit dizzy and nauseous.
There is a lot to think about right now,
so it's affecting my body.
Did you think about me too?
Yeah.
Come on,
I thought you'd flirt back
and say, "I missed you."
Sorry,
I'm a bit out of it right now.
I couldn't come up with that in time.
Is it related to your brain?
Yeah.
I used to have amnesia.
I still can't remember everything,
but it's like...
my memories are coming back.
Would you like to remember?
I don't know.
Both trying to remember
and not being able to remember
make me suffer.
Why don't you stop thinking about it?
If you're happy with how things are now,
why not just stay in the present?
You really think so?
Mm.
I lost my dog, whom I loved dearly.
My friend felt bad for me,
so they gave me a replica dog.
When I saw it,
it made me even sadder
because it reminded me
that I'd already lost my dog.
A dog?
What was their name?
"Kiiro."
Kiiro?
Yes,
it means "yellow."
My fish is also named "Kiiro."
Sun,
have we known each other before?
Nadear.
Why did you go outside without telling me?
I just wanted to take a walk.
Get some rest.
We still have three months, don't we?
Less than three months.
Look at you.
You don't want to be a pretty doctor, huh?
I'm still pretty.
Yeah, yeah.
Why did you do that?
Just say the truth and everything will be resolved.
I don't understand. Why didn't you tell her?
Because the fact that Chris loves me
doesn't make what I did right.
You weren't the only one at fault.
If her memories hurt her...
The only thing I want right now
is for her to love me.
If she loves me,
I'll tell her what we used to be.
I want to be sure
that she will forgive me first.
Alright.
[Third Person]
Nadear...
Chris betrayed me.
She betrayed me again, Jeen.
I lost my dog, whom I loved dearly.
A dog?
What was their name?
Kiiro.
Did your name come from the word "yellow" as well?
Kiiro...
Kiiro is hungry.
Come on.
Go.
Time to eat. Let's go.
Nadear...
Kiiro...
Chris, come eat your breakfast.
I made some for you, too.
Thanks.
Don't forget to take your medicine after your meal.
Nadear,
where did our dog go?
What dog?
Our dog.
I remember we used to have a dog.
Chris, we've never had a dog.
We have.
Our dog...
The other Kiiro.
Chris.
Listen to me.
We've never had a dog.
The only possibility is that dog.
Nan once asked us to take care of her Corgi.
Its fur is brown and white.
She left it with us when she flew overseas.
It's smart,
affectionate,
and it likes sitting on your lap.
Was it Nan's dog?
Yeah.
I'll go to the restaurant today, then.
Don't.
I want you to rest.
So this is what
you want me to do?
To give Chris freedom?
To let Chris love someone else?
I don't know what to do anymore, Jeen.
Even her memories don't seem to be enough to make her mine.
Our brains are complex.
Chris remembers you,
but she still had an affair.
Perhaps...
her memories alone aren't enough.
You first have to know
what Chris is planning to do.
If I do, Chris will be mine again, right?
Welcome, Chris.
Can I stay with you tonight?
My place is your place.
Should I change my hairstyle?
Why?
I want to be a new me.
No need to do that.
I like you just the way you are.
Thanks.
We're friends, so let's stop here.
But we've gone a lot further than this.
If you realize that, then you should keep a proper distance.
Okay.
Tonight...
Let's just hold hands.
Just hold hands.
Well, I'm just holding your hand,
nothing more.
But isn't this too close?
Friends can be this close.
This is weird.
Why did you suddenly ask me to meet you in private?
Didn't Nadear say you were sick?
Have you ever had a dog?
A Corgi.
I'm a cat person.
I've never had a dog before.
Kiiro.
Whose dog is it?
I don't think it's true that we've never known each other before.
Kiiro.
It's not a coincidence, right?
I just want to know the truth.
Who I am right now
is the truth.
Ever since I lost my memories...
Love was just attachment.
We should break up.
Whoever dares to take Chris away from me
will die.
To overcome your fear,
you'll have to face it.
I'll be with you.
♫The rain keeps splashing beneath our cover,♫
♫Once it was a special place for two lovers♫
♫There was never enough room for the third♫
♫Now, the rain soaks our hearts together♫
♫The question that's trapped in my heart♫
♫Maybe it's time for you to do your part♫
♫Choose the one your heart truly desires♫
♫Before the last raindrop falls, don't make me shed another tear♫